I didn't stare.
Stared.
- I wasn't staring...
- Hey!
Why the hell were you staring so disgustingly?
Do you want to die?
Instead of an apology
you keep making excuses.
- Sorry...
- Oh, damn.
Why were you staring?
I didn't stare.
You looked.
You'd like it if you're such a schmuck
how are you, looked at you?
Hansik says he is disgusted.
- Sorry.
- Come to your senses.
- Why were you looking, huh?
Lost your fear?
- Sorry.
- Stop apologizing.
- Yes, you got it!
Do you want to die?
Want?
What are you doing here?
Help.
What?
Nobody will help you.
It's just you...
you...
figure it out yourself.
Good luck.
What is this?
Are you crazy?
Do you want to stab me with this?
What? "Help"?
Hey, stab me.
Come on.
Stab me.
Pyrni. Do you think you can?
Punch me, you schmuck.
Stab me, stab me.
- Hey, Junil!
- Junil!
Hey Junil!
Are you okay?
You're bleeding!
You think you're cool
when you mock the weak, right?
Save.
What?
- Save me.
- OK.
I'll save you.
Stop it!
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop it, hey!
Stop it!
- Move away.
- Stop it already, damn it!
Stop what, bastard?
These people need to be killed.
No?
Hey Kim Eugyeom, hey!
That's enough.
What? What's enough?
These bastards need to be beaten
half to death to...
Stop it already!
Don't go!
OK.
But we must be different.
Hey.
Have you ever smoked?
A couple of times in high school.
I can't smoke.
Only my throat hurts.
How does it feel? When do you smoke?
At that moment
I really wanted to smoke a cigarette.
And I thought: “This is probably
why do people smoke?
Listen.
Then you've gone too far.
What?
Something almost happened.
You were too excited.
He grabbed the pipe first.
This bastard probably
constantly beat children.
We don't have to be the same.
How are we different?
We are different.
We...
We only hit bad guys.
What?
Hey Kang Yoongi.
That's what you suggested.
You wanted this, didn't you?
Wait, I'll answer now and come back.
Yes, mom.
Chison?
Yes, I understand, I'll come right away.
Yes, yes.
Quicker!
I need to leave urgently.
Let's go quickly, I need to change clothes.
Faster.
How did you write the trial exam?
What do you think?
What's the last answer? Crap.
Isn't it four?
Look here.
They say they beat up the hooligans from Kyonungo.
Two people wearing masks?
What's happened? Let me see.
I've heard about it.
There's a guy from Somun studying at my school.
They say that those hooligans
beaten by two masked men.
And they couldn't fight back.
Who are they?
Bloggers?
I wish they would come to our school
and taught school bullies a lesson.
Exactly.
Maybe I should write a post?
For them to come.
Cool, write it down.
Where to post?
Yes, anywhere.
Anywhere?
What if hooligans see this?
Instead of masked avengers, they will come.
Stop talking nonsense.
Yoongi has arrived.
- Come on in.
- Hello.
Chison.
Do you remember me?
What a relief.
I'm so glad.
Yoongi...
I was very worried about you.
I came to see you every month.
Why do you sleep for so long?
Damn, that's so good.
Chison, thank you.
Thank you.
There are two left.
I won't leave it to them like this.
Yes, I feel much better.
Yes, director.
I think I'll be able to go to work soon.
I'll start next week.
Yes.
My husband returned from work.
See you next week then.
Yes.
Tomorrow at lunch
workers will come and clean that room.
That room?
Which room?
Tell.
Whose room do you mean?
I think this room is for Eugyeom
prevents you from concentrating.
This room needs to be cleaned.
I'm asking, whose room is this?
Whose room is this?
Why can't you say
what is this Sugyeom's room?
Why can't you say his name?
We...
enough suffering.
Now we need to focus on Uigyeom.
Have you noticed that lately Euigyeom...
changed?
Every day he has
new abrasions on the face.
What do you mean?
You don't see it, do you?
You're only interested in his grades.
How Sugyeom experienced
stress and beat up Eugyeom,
So Eigyom began to get into fights.
I'm home.
Kim Eugyom.
Eigyom, go to the room.
Yes.
Give me your cassette player.
For what?
He said give it back, so give it away.
Why are you walking around with this old thing?
Will you contradict your father?
Get to the room, quickly!
Eugyom!
I said, give me the cassette player!
Dad...
This is my brother's favorite thing.
You wanted me to be like him.
What?
Did I do something wrong?
Dad...
Do you even know why his brother loved him?
What?
He said that if you put on headphones,
then you can go where there is no dad.
That's the problem, puppy.
He was a weakling...
that's why it happened.
I couldn't stand it.
Couldn't stand it!
It's you...
killed him.
Eugyom.
Dad...
you really...
Do you want me to be like a brother?
Come to your senses, please.
Eugyom.
Mom is the same.
You and dad...
killed my brother.
Pi Toil, Tenam School.
On the second floor there is a closed bar.
He's there now.
Don't be like last time.
Why?
They're the bad guys.
We must be different from them.
AND…
You've been looking dangerous lately.
Don't worry.
We are different.
My God, you are all gathered here.
Tenam School Elite.
Wow, he really came.
Is it you? Psychos in masks?
They defeated Namhyop, they defeated Kiyun.
So, is it my turn now?
Who are you?
You sucked up to our Gwanphal,
and he told you that we are here?
But what to do now?
Kwanphal said that too
wants to be with you, and has given you all up.
Right, Gwangphal?
Are you laughing?
If you can escape
run.
It seems like something went wrong.
Are you cowardly?
I?
Come here!
Die!
Eugyom!
Damn...
Eugyeom, are you okay?
Yes.
Get up.
You fight well, Red Mask.
Let's figure this out.
Wait!
Who are you, man?
What?
Kang Yoon?
May I die...
Fucking nerd. I'm shocked.
Hey.
Who are you?
Are you taking revenge on us?
- Because of that asshole Chisung?
- Let go, you bastards!
What's wrong with him?
Stand still.
Who are you?
High school superhero.
This bastard!
Come on, Pi Toil!
Kang Yoongi.
Are you crazy?
A! Damn...
How to finish him off?
Hey, come out! Come out, bastard!
Eugyom!
- Come here!
- Eigyom!
Come here!
Catch him!
Fast, damn it!
Come out!
Hey!
Run!
Stand!
Catch him!
A! He's very fast!
Oh Kim Seungjoon!
Need help?
Faster!
Forward, forward, forward!
Vali, I'm working.
Sorry.
This motorcycle...
I saved you today.
Get out already!
Now we're even.
I need to make a delivery.
Thank you.
Eugyom.
I need to say something.
What?
Revenge again?
Hey Kang Yoongi.
You thought I wouldn't understand
even after what I saw?
Kim Seungjoon.
May I ask?
Can I spend the night at your place?
I can't come home like this.
Please.
Sorry to put you down at the gym.
But if I bring you home like this,
I'll have problems.
My dad...
I'm glad I came to my senses.
Hey.
Do you seem to be good at boxing?
Dude,
I was just walking with Chihyuk and Hongil
and didn't cause any problems.
I was preparing for the Asian Games.
You know...
I was the best in my weight category.
As soon as I entered high school, I
after the first match I became the best again.
You're kind of weird right now.
Don't fight anymore
Don't hang out with people like Yoongi.
Just like before, put on your headphones and study.
You have good grades and a rich family,
what to worry about?
There are many people at school who have never fought
and is released without problems.
And these fights...
the one who fought once
will fight again, understand?
Why don't you answer?
Aren't these the parents?
Don't want.
The model student is rebelling today.
When I first took up boxing,
I was really scared of punching people in the face.
and receive a response.
It's the same in a fight.
It's difficult at first.
It's scary to hit and be beaten.
And then you stop being afraid.
And from that moment on there was a fight
becomes very natural.
It becomes a habit.
You don't fight because there is a reason.
You create a reason.
Because it's a habit.
Kim Seungjoon, you speak well.
Suddenly.
All this time...
I was just showing off like a child.
Better just learn boxing.
Don't fight, just learn boxing, damn it.
Answer, parents will worry.
I'll spend the night with a friend.
- Sorry, teacher.
- Nothing.
Today my child will be late.
Sorry.
Everything is fine.
Then I'll come tomorrow.
Sorry, my son was never like that.
Nothing.
Don't go out.
See you tomorrow.
Have a nice trip.
Kang Yoon?
Is this the Kang Yoon we know?
Yes.
Then who is this guy next to him?
He's funny.
Hey, who are you?
High school superhero, beast.
"High School Superhero"?
I don't know him.
Namhyup says he knows him.
Not very good.
I saw him at my father's alumni meeting.
He was not associated with us.
Anyway
weren't you beaten?
Lee Kiyun.
Ah, idiots, really.
Meet my friends
from high school.
Hello.
But...
What the hell are you doing somewhere?
to get beaten up
and then came to complain to the elders?
Idiot.
But what can you do?
He may be an idiot, but he is a friend.
So what should we do?
Hands? Legs?
What exactly?
As you see fit.
Namhyup...
What is the honor student from Seomun doing here?
Didn't your father send you
to Seomun so you can study?
You should go by
in his father's footsteps and become a doctor.
Then you can help me in the future.
Lee Chisung woke up yesterday.
Who?
The one who abandoned us?
And what?
So what?
Wasn't he himself alienated because of his studies?
Your father knows this better than anyone.
But your father is truly amazing.
Was this two or three years ago?
Are you still doing this?
You're stubborn, huh?
Scary.
That's the only way doctors become.
So, did you find out about the school?
I asked around in high school.
He entered Yongseong.
Yongsung?
Escaped to a neighboring area?
I'll go there tomorrow.
Do it as I see fit?
Namhyup.
This time give me more money.
We're friends.
You look for me only at such moments.
I'm very upset.
This time give it to me
more pocket money.
A?
What are you always looking at here?
Like crazy.
Can't see it?
- What?
- Airplane.
So are you looking at the plane?
But do you hear everything even in this?
This?
They are broken, there is no sound.
So, the civil revolution is...
this is cutting off the king's head,
which suppresses
freedom and rights of citizens.
This is the civil revolution.
After the introduction of the civil revolution
civil society is coming.
What is the most striking example
How do citizens become masters?
Democracy and republic.
Right.
And then there is the constitutional monarchy.
- You really don’t know?
- Don't know.
Just answer if you know, okay?
Your friends?
Who are you?
You're not Kang Yoon, are you?
This idiot doesn't know anything.
What?
You are not Kang Yoongi.
Bring Kang Yoongi.
For free?
What is the price?
50.
Okay.
Here you go.
Crap.
Let go.
Come here.
Aren't you coming?
Then I'll do it myself.
Hey.
Is that all? A?
All?
Get up, damn it, get up.
What's happened?
What is it?
Damn, hey, it hurts.
Hurt.
It hurts, it hurts, damn it.
I said it hurt.
It hurts, damn it.
Is this what you should do?
What? Hurt?
And it turns out it hurts so much.
Hey.
What is this, a match? Are you giving up?
Grit your teeth.
Easily breaks.
Crap.
I'm in pain.
I said it hurts, it hurts!
I said it hurt, damn it.
Some kind of poverty
makes me waste my energy.
Hey, go get Kang Yoongi.
Bring it.
Kang Yoongi.
Someone has come for you.
Who?
I don't know.
They are looking for you and Yigyoma, they say they will catch you.
Sonny was crippled.
If you get caught, it will be bad.
Oh, Kang Yoon.
Long time no see.
Who are you?
High school superhero.
Wow.
What is this? Concept?
Ha, funny.
You talk a lot.
Hey, recess is short.
Eugyom.
Step aside, this is my business.
I said go away.
Choi Kisu.
You need to fight me.
Why? I'm more interested in him.
What, is it childish to take revenge, or what?
Won't you run away today?
Get out while you can.